RASHMI V

CONTACT

- +91 8123794357
- venkatesh.rashmi92@gmail.com
- JP Nagar- Bengaluru

STRENGTHS

EXCELLENT COMMUNICATION SKILLS. BOTH IN VERBAL AND WRITING.

PEOPLE MANAGEMENT.

ADAPTABILITY.

EDUCATION

MBA-FINANCE

Dayananda Sagar Business Accademy 2013-2015

ACHIVEMENTS

SPOT AWARD: MORE THAN 8 MONTHS FOR KEEPING QUALITY AT 99%.

STAR PERFORMER.

SERVICE EXCELLENCE AWARD FOR PROVIDING GOOD CUSTOMER RESOULTION.

PROFILE

Obtain a challenging position and to be part of professional management team by applying creative problem solving and management skills. Also, to make use of my interpersonal skills to achieve goals of a company that focuses on customer satisfaction and customer experience.

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR RESEARCH SPECIALIST - RESEARCH DEPARTMENT

Ocwen Finanical Services - November 2017- till date

The Research department is responsible for researching and responding to written inquiries and complaints received from customer's regarding their mortgage accounts. Further co-ordinate with other business departments such as Legal, Underwriting, Payoff, Credit Reporting, Tax Department, Private Mortgage Insurance, Ombudsman, Year End, Title and Lien release etc, to resolve customers complaints.

Roles and Responsibilities

- Responding to Research questions and implementing changes to resolve the customer query with professional language
- Ensuring appropriate resolutions are provided within the time limits and followed up till final resolution.
- · Identified process gaps and shared root cause analysis.
- Handled a team of 5 employees and handing end to end responsibilities for the team ensuring optimal resource utilization.
- · Worked on the priority and the escalated cases.
- Part of the escalated call with the different departments to discuss and obtain the resolution on the team pending cases.
- Handling process refresher training for OJT and existing teams.
- Maintaining healthy relationship between the department to coordinate and provide the findings to the customers.
- · Generating daily or monthly production reports.
- Worked on I-case and PHH transition update project and got appraised by the manager for the work done.
- Conducting Fun activities every week being a part of Fun Committee.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: 18-08-1992

Nationality: Indian

Husband Name: Sathish B

KEY PROJECTS

- Analyzing the root cause of the critical errors and sharing an action plan to the internal team.
- During the PHH transition, worked on the highly escalated cases and was able to assist the customer with the timely resolution.
- · Helped in creating the Macro for attorney representation project
- Created an SOP (Standard Operating Procedure) when handling the team.

PRIOR WORK EXPERIENCE

ANALYST - BREAKFREE AND FHOG

Australia and New Zealand Service - November 2015 - May 2017

My role involved in assessing and processing of Breakfree request and analyzing the application on several parameters to determine the eligibility of customers, like transaction history, Mortgage Lending's and Credit cards.

Roles and Responsibilities

- Handling the daily allocation for night shift and weekend login.
- · Assessing customer's eligibility and registering for Breakfree Package.
- Responsible of allocating loans to the agents when the supervisor is not on floor.
- Managing the additional activities like running the Macro and conducting the fun activities

ALL THE ABOVE MENTIONED INFORMATION IS TRUE AND ACCURATE TO THE BEST OF MY KNOWLEDGE

DATE:

PLACE: BENGALURU (RASHMI)